Subscribe to my channel!
This video is about my trip to Ehime, Japan.
I went to Ehime this time because I had a ticket to Ehime for a wave travel. I decided to go there by myself because I wanted to travel alone.
I ate a rice ball on the plane.
I think I made this onigiri from the leftover rice from the previous day and brought it with me.
I went to bed right after eating it!
Ta-da! Mikyan!
So we arrived at Ehime Matsuyama Airport safely! And now we are moving again!
I am heading for Dogo Onsen because the hotel is located near Dogo Onsen.
The station was very fashionable!
And the Bocchan train was waiting for us.
It looks like an endless train!
This is also the Bocchan Karakuri Clock that often comes up when you search for "Dogo Onsen".
I wanted to see it at the time of the Karakuri Clock, so I decided to walk to the hotel anyway.
This is the shopping street on the way to the hotel.
The sea bream rice looks really delicious!
While I was saying that, we have arrived at the hotel, the Dogo Hiroo, where we will be staying this time.
It wasn't time to check in yet, so I left my luggage at the front desk for now.
We went to a restaurant called "Daikokuya" for lunch!
For lunch, we went to an udon restaurant called Daikokuya!
I had a refreshing dish called "Bishamon Udon"!
It was really refreshing!
As you can see, it was really refreshing cold udon!
It was really delicious and smooth!
After eating the udon, it started to rain outside.
I took out my umbrella that I had brought with me!
I had brought a folding umbrella!
Rain was in the forecast!
Anyway, this Kumamon umbrella
The Kumamon from the inside is a little too scary.
I like Kumamon, but I thought it was a little scary.
Well, it's raining, so I'm going back to the shopping street.
I found a towel shop.
There are so many nice towels!
I bought some souvenirs here!
Chakuchi mandarin juice is located in the back of the shop.
So I went to the back of the shop to buy some Chaguchi mandarin oranges.
I went to the back of the shop.
There it is! Chaguchi Mikan Juice!
I decided to try the three kinds of juice!
This is the Chaguchi Mikan Juice!
On this day, there were 4 kinds of mandarin juices to choose from.
One of them was on vacation.
So I had to choose my favorite juice from the 4 kinds with this faucet.
I was so worried!
Three quarters of three.
I couldn't drink one kind.
I'm not sure which one I'm not going to drink anymore.
I mean, I was really worried about which three to drink.
How many times faster is this speed?
After much deliberation
Kiyomi, Kawachi Mamaki, and Unshu.
Let's compare them!
I wondered if you could tell the difference between the mikan juices.
As you are nodding your head, they are quite different.
The sourness, the sweetness...
They are totally different!
I think
I like this one
I like this one.
Maybe Unshu
After drinking the mandarin juice
I wanted to take the city train.
Yes, take the city train
We came to a further part of the city
I came further into the city
But it was still raining too hard
It was raining too hard
There is a castle ahead
But as expected, we gave up.
Anyway, since I came all the way here
I went through the arcade of the Tokaido
The atmosphere of the arcade
It was very similar to Shimodori in Kumamoto.
And I found a coffee shop called Amanda Coffees.
I had never heard of this name, so I searched for it.
They only have a store in Ehime, so I had no choice but to drink this local coffee.
So I had no choice but to drink this local coffee!
Today's coffee is Amanda Coffee's!
I didn't mention that I was in Ehime when I posted this on my instagram.
I was hiding it, so I'm glad I was able to put it up on this nalsub!
Now, after my coffee, I'm back in front of Dogo Onsen station!
I thought I could see the clock at 5 o'clock. So I went to Ashu Cafe Bocchan to kill some time!
I came to Asheu Cafe Botchan to kill some time!
I called my mom and she sent me a lot of data about Ehime.
One of them was this "Ashu Cafe Bocchan"!
One of them was this Asheu Cafe Bocchan.
It was indoors, so I could take shelter from the rain, and my feet were tired from the trip, so it was very soothing.
They had a snake bone store right in front of the cafe, and we were allowed to bring in our own food, so we were able to fill our stomachs a little!
It was delicious! It was almost 5 o'clock!
It was almost 5:00 p.m. and time to go to the Karakuri Clock! Thank you very much for your help at Asheu Cafe Bocchan!
I was able to arrive at the Karakuri Clock just in time for 5 o'clock, and was able to see the clock amidst the crowd of people!
After the clock, I checked in with Mr. Hiroo Dogo.
Here's a full view of the hotel room I'll be staying in today.
Here's a full view of the hotel room I'll be staying in today!
Well...
I'm alone, but thank you for the twin room.
It's a very comfortable room.
Here's the bathroom. We're starting our room tour now.
Here's the bathroom. And here's the bathroom.
This is a very beautiful hotel!It's a very beautiful hotel.
Yes, yay!
Yay!
And let me introduce today's coordination.
I love this jacket that looks like a mandarin orange!
I love the mandarin-like jacket!
All done and dusted.
I'm stretching as hard as I can.
He's stretching a lot, isn't he?
I'm done.
Oh, yes!
I bought a delicious pudding called "Dogo Pudding" on the way to the hotel!
I'm going to eat it during my stay!
Now, I'm going to take a rest.
After a short rest, I was hungry, so we went out to eat!
This time, we went to Matsuyama Thai Rice Aka for dinner!
Yes, Thai rice!
I came here to eat Thai rice, but this restaurant is... Oh, wait a minute, it's open!
Look at the Thai rice, it looks so delicious!
I'm sure some of you have seen this Thai rice restaurant on the Tao Sub Chan, but Gebo also had Thai rice at this restaurant.
Since it was recommended, we decided to go there for sure!
It was so hot! The rice was freshly cooked!
It was so delicious!
Delicious!
I want to say "delicious," but...
I want to say it's good, but I'll put it down at first sight and be quiet.
And put some condiments.
and eat it with this broth!
Tai-meshi rice in chazuke style!
This way of eating is also really delicious!
Here we go!
Isn't it delicious?
I could tell by your face, right?
I liked this way of eating it.
Yes, I finished it off. It was very delicious!
I went back to the hotel and changed into a yukata. I'm finally going to the hot spring!
I'm off!
After the bath, the hot spring was so nice!
My skin is so smooth and shiny! And after the bath, I'm going to drink some milk!
I bought this milk at a convenience store.
It was delicious!
I don't really know the difference in taste, but it's nice to drink local milk, isn't it?
Well, it seems I'm ready for bed, so I'm going to sleep now.
I thought I was going to go to bed, but I've decided to take a video of the front of my yukata.
I thought I'd take a video of the front of the yukata, but it was so cute.
Good morning.
So the second day started with breakfast at the hotel!
The juice above is Pon juice!
After breakfast, we also had today's coffee!
I went back to my room and finished my hair and makeup.
I ate the Dogo pudding I bought yesterday!
Dogo pudding with two layers of pudding and fruit jelly!
I'm going to try it right away!
First, the fruit jelly!
It has a whole mandarin orange in it!
Look, it's big!
The mandarin oranges are so delicious!
Yes, I ate this one in one bite, too!
It's a big mouthful!
And the bottom is pudding!
The pudding is so smooth.
I ate it all in one go.
I know it's a little late to say this, but since we're in a hotel, they should have talked to us...
I finished the pudding while I was at the warehouse.
Thank you for the pudding, it was delicious!
I checked out of the hotel.
Thank you very much, Mr. Hiroo Dogo!
Well, I'm going on another trip today!
My backpack... it's filled to the brim with all my belongings!
It's heavy, but let's enjoy the second day of our trip!
I'm going to take a city tram right away!
Today I bought a one-day ticket, which allows me to ride as many trams as I want.
Yes, it's a great deal!
Here we are at Matsuyama City Station!
The reason I came to Matsuyama City Station is because I wanted to leave my backpack at the station.
I left it in the locker and took the city train again!
Unlimited ride is the best!
Here we are at Tokaido!
Since I gave up yesterday, I came to the Tokaido Highway... today is the day!
I'm walking again toward Matsuyama Castle.
There seems to be a ropeway
So I am walking towards there!
Once again, I am so glad that the weather is fine today!
As I was walking, I found a jakoten shop.
I found a jakoten shop!
This is the same Shinonobe Hippoboko that I saw on TaoSub!
I was sure I was going to eat there because the jicama looked so good!
I bought it right away. I'm going to eat it!
Mmmm! Delicious!
It was really delicious because it was warm and freshly baked.
After eating, we went to the rope station.
I was about to get on the rope, but then I saw a lift,
What? The lift? So I got on the lift.
It was the lift I was expecting.
It was the only one. Once again, I was glad that the weather was fine.
It had been a long time since I rode a lift at an amusement park. I was a little nervous, but it felt great.
We arrived safely near the castle.
Now we will go on foot from here. The castle wall looks like a castle.
But we still can't see Matsuyama Castle.
Oh, what if this is...
I didn't know dandelions bloomed in such a place!I never thought dandelions would bloom in a place like this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When I see a dandelion, I get dandelion blood in my veins.
While I'm talking about that...
Look! We've come to a spot where we can see the whole of Matsuyama City!
You can see the whole city!
And then, what? The castle! You can also see the castle!
Yoshiaki and Matsuyama Castle
While I was taking this picture, a tourist took a picture of me.
The only chance to get a glimpse of the castle!
And since we're here, let's take a look at the inside of Matsuyama Castle! There are a lot of things on display!
I don't know much about it, but it was amazing! And the view from the Angel Pavilion, but my face was too backlit!
Here's just the view.
It felt so good!
It felt so good. I felt great!
Matsuyama Castle was a very nice castle!
After climbing the castle!
After climbing the castle, we had Iyokan shaved ice! We wanted to make this summer the summer of shaved ice!
I wanted to eat shaved ice this summer!
So, let's eat it now!
I can already remember. It was really good.
Hey, it's delicious. It's like...
It's kind of tasty. It's got, like, Iokan peel in the syrup. It was really sweet and sour.
It was really sweet and sour.
It was really delicious!
I ate it up!
And you know what, the waiter here
When I was getting permission for this video...
What channel is this? He asked me, "What channel?
I said, "The Marutao Channel.
I told him it was the Marutao Channel.
He searched for it.
And he even subscribed to my channel!
and subscribed to our channel! I'm so happy!
I hope you guys are watching!
The shaved ice
It was really delicious!
Thank you so much!
And
And the store kindly offered us some tangerine juice, tea, and mandarin orange juice.
The shop staff was so kind to provide us with a bottle of tangerine juice!
This tangerine juice is also really good!
It's refreshing, and since it was so hot, I could drink as many glasses of it as I wanted.
I took the lift on the way back!
I love it so much! It was so much fun I wanted to ride the lift one more time!
After getting off the lift, we went to a green tea store called "Foggy Forest" on the same street as before!
I had been told about this place by a fan, so I bought some as souvenirs!
I really enjoyed the Matsuyama Castle area!
Now we are on the way to the Matsuyama Civic Hall!
I took a tram to get here!
This is where my teammates are going on their national tour in Ehime!
Well, we've been here once, right?
Yes, it's a pilgrimage to a holy place.
And now we're on the move again.
Here we are in front of the Ferris wheel, Kururin.
Why am I in front of the Ferris wheel?
It's right in front of the Ferris wheel!
You got a free ticket for the Ferris wheel with the unlimited train ride
and a free ticket for the Ferris wheel!
What a great deal!
I had no choice but to ride the Ferris wheel!
So I decided to ride the Ferris wheel for the first time in my life!
For the first time in my life
I rode the Ferris wheel by myself for the first time in my life!
All by myself!
Oh my God!
My first time on a Ferris wheel by myself!
It's fun, but it's a good feeling.
If I could ride a Ferris wheel, I would be able to travel alone.
I think I can do everything by myself.
I can do everything by myself!
I didn't say a single word at the hotel.
But when I got on the Ferris wheel, I couldn't help talking!
It's a surrealistic picture, but I really enjoyed this one-man Ferris wheel ride.
I enjoyed the Ferris wheel so much that I am definitely stronger now that I've been on this trip!
Well, I'm back at Matsuyama Airport soon!
My face!
Like this!
Last meal in Matsuyama!
My last meal was Thai rice!
You may think it's Thai rice again...
There is another way to eat Thai rice.
This one is called Uwajima Thai rice.
Mix soup stock and raw egg.
Then, mix in the Thai sashimi.
Seaweed is also added.
Mix it well with the sauce.
Then, put an appropriate amount of rice in a bowl.
Mix the sauce well, and put the Thai fish on the rice.
Finally, pour the dashi broth over the rice and eat it.
This way of eating Thai rice is genius!
It was geniusly delicious!
So much so that it was a completely different dish from the first day's Thai rice.
It was so different from the first day's Thai rice!
This Thai rice was also really delicious!
I think even I like this one better.
It was so refreshing!
After we finished eating, we went to Mican Garden in the airport!
It was delicious!
There was no one there, so we had the whole Mikan experience to ourselves!
(By monopolizing, I mean just taking lots of pictures...)Exclusive, but only to take lots of pictures
I did it!
It was already time for my flight!
I bought a lot of souvenirs and had a fun trip to Matsuyama by myself!
Thank you for watching until the end!
Bye bye!